<resources>
    <string name="app_name">P2PFinancial</string>
    <string name="main_frag_name">Silicon valley rainbow novice program</string>
    <string name="main_frag_txt_one">Principal and interest security</string>
    <string name="main_frag_txt_two">The daily rate</string>
    <string name="main_frag_txt_three">High yield</string>
    <string name="main_frag_apr">Expected annual interest rate :8.00%</string>
    <string name="main_frag_btn">Join now</string>
    <string name="main_frag_safeguard">Risk protection is regulated by silicon valley Banks</string>
    <string name="item_angle"><![CDATA[>]]></string>
    <string name="allinvest_money">Amount of product</string>
    <string name="item_thousand">ten thousand</string>
    <string name="allinvest_apr">Expected annual interest rate</string>
    <string name="item_symbol">%</string>
    <string name="item_safeguard">Principal and interest security</string>
    <string name="allinvest_lockup">Lock period</string>
    <string name="item_day">day</string>
    <string name="invest_slogan">   Silicon valley finance is on a roll, with returns of up to $188   </string>
    <string name="loading_test">Data is on its way...</string>
    <string name="more_text_regist">user registration</string>
    <string name="more_text_secret">gesture password </string>
    <string name="more_text_reset">Reset gesture password</string>
    <string name="more_contact_phone">010-56253825</string>
    <string name="more_text_contact">contact the customer service </string>
    <string name="more_text_sms">user feedback </string>
    <string name="more_text_share">Share with friends</string>
    <string name="more_text_about">About managing money in silicon valley</string>
    <string name="login_study">Study tips:</string>
    <string name="login_buy">Recharge we will demonstrate the recharge function by integrating the payment amount of alipay SDK</string>
    <string name="login_contact_text">Withdrawal business: in p2p financial platform, withdrawals are not delivered to the account in real time, but are reviewed. The system will inform you of the transfer within 24 hours. If you have not received it, please contact the customer service.</string>
    <string name="login_invest_manage">Investment management (intuitive)</string>
    <string name="login_investment_manage">Investment management</string>
    <string name="login_money_manage">assets management</string>
    <string name="register_phone">phone:</string>
    <string name="put_phone">Please enter your cell phone number</string>
    <string name="register_user">username:</string>
    <string name="put_user">Please enter user name</string>
    <string name="register_pwd">password:</string>
    <string name="put_pwd">Please enter your password</string>
    <string name="register_password">confirm password:</string>
    <string name="put_password">Please confirm the password</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>
    <string name="consult_register">consultative department</string>
    <string name="invest_register">The ministry of finance</string>
    <string name="skill_register">technical division</string>
    <string name="feedback_register">user feedback </string>
    <string name="feedback_send">send:</string>
    <string name="feedback_message">message:</string>
    <string name="feedback_problem">Feedback any problems you encounter to customer service staff</string>
    <string name="feedback_no">cancel</string>
    <string name="feedback_yes">confirm</string>
    <string name="about_it">Silicon valley finance is affiliated with shang silicon valley IT education brand</string>
    <string name="www_atguigu_com">Silicon valley finance (www.atguigu.com) is an independent brand operated by shang silicon valley (China).Silicon valley finance is a professional company that provides financial services to users based on Internet technology.</string>
    <string name="about_good">Since its launch in 2014, silicon valley finance has been widely trusted and praised by users.At present, the "silicon valley finance" service covers more than 30 provinces, municipalities and autonomous regions in China. It has successfully helped users to obtain loans and made them obtain stable and high returns.</string>
    <string name="about_system">Silicon valley finance has perfect management system, excellent management team, standard operation process, strict risk control measures, and provides comprehensive professional micro-finance and wealth management consulting services for users at both ends of the platform, such as consulting, evaluation, financial planning, protocol management and so on.</string>
    <string name="about_pattern">Silicon valley finance has perfect management system, excellent management team, standard operation process, strict risk control measures, and provides comprehensive professional micro-finance and wealth management consulting services for users at both ends of the platform, such as consulting, evaluation, financial planning, protocol management and so on.Financial in silicon valley is the valley of financial in his personal microfinance for individuals as the main mode, by lenders to provide reliable, steady, high return on investment of financial products, to the borrower to provide fast, convenient, long-term stability of low-cost funds between channels, to build a transparent, convenient and equality of network financial transaction service platform.Silicon valley finance has benefited from a strict pricing system for individual financial risks and a safe and diversified investment mechanism, which can fully protect and satisfy the interests of both borrowers and lenders.</string>
    <string name="about_develop">With the vigorous development of Internet finance today, silicon valley finance has been continuously exploring innovative models, and is committed to becoming an outstanding Internet finance enterprise to boost the development of individual finance and inclusive finance.</string>
    <string name="recharge_text">Please enter the recharge amount</string>
    <string name="recharge_money">recharge amount </string>
    <string name="recharge_money_residue">Your account is currently available：</string>
    <string name="text_rmb">$</string>
    <string name="recharge_btn_text">recharge</string>
    <string name="recharge_hint">warm prompt ：</string>
    <string name="recharge_introduce">1. All investment deposits will be managed by the third-party platform.2. Online and offline recharge commission is free.3, please pay attention to your bank card recharge limit, so as not to cause inconvenience.4, if the recharge into the account did not arrive in time, please contact customer service.5, prohibit credit card cash, false transactions and other behavior, has been found will be punished, including but not limited to: limited collection, frozen accounts, permanent suspension of services, etc.6. If the amount recharged in your account is for investment in financial services on this platform, the application can only be made after 3 months.7. If the value has been charged in the mobile phone client, the card can only be used in the computer or mobile phone.Unless the original card is lost, damaged or deactivated, the bound card will not be replaced.In this case, please contact the customer service and provide written evidence provided by the bank.</string>
</resources>
